[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did actor Liam Neeson voice in the 2008 movie The Chronicles of Narnia: Prince Caspian?", "correct_answer": "The lion Aslan", "incorrect_answers": ["Trumpkin the dwarf", "Asterius the Minotaur", "Bulgy Bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All dogs, cats and birds are colorblind.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed has a wild markings and is a crossbreed between an Asian Leopard Cat and a domestic cat.", "correct_answer": "Bengal", "incorrect_answers": ["Ocicat", "Savannah", "California Spangled Cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the 1998 animated movie in which Kevin Spacey voiced an evil grasshopper named Hopper?", "correct_answer": "A Bugs Life", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ant Bully", "The Ant and the Grasshopper", "Antz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Woody Allen movie depicts a future with robot butlers?", "correct_answer": "Sleeper", "incorrect_answers": ["Match Point", "Stardust Memories", "Cassandras Dream"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Jefferson was a leading opponent of the metric system.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mixing baking soda and vinegar in a closed container causes a tiny explosion.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As the most ardent consumers of absinthe, the French produced these amounts in 1910, just for domestic use.", "correct_answer": "36 million liters", "incorrect_answers": ["15 million liters", "11 million liters", "10 million liters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What body of water feeds the Dead Sea?", "correct_answer": "The Jordan River", "incorrect_answers": ["The Euphrates River", "The Mediterranean Ocean", "The Red Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these peaks is the highest?", "correct_answer": "McKinley (Alaska)", "incorrect_answers": ["Grossglockner (Austria)", "Mont Blanc (France)", "Mount Elbert (Colorado)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title to this 1989 Wayne Wang comedy:  Life is Cheap...", "correct_answer": "... But Toilet Paper is Expensive.", "incorrect_answers": ["... Dont Spend It All in One Place.", "... Tivo the Good Parts.", "... And There Are No Refunds!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who or what is Vinson Massif?", "correct_answer": "The tallest mountain in Antarctica", "incorrect_answers": ["Sanitations third cousin, twice removed", "The third king of Sweden", "a muscle in the human body"]}]